cakewalk.com 2018-11-26

# Cakewalk Privacy Policy

###  Cakewalk by BandLab is free.   
Get the award-winning DAW now. 

Following the acquisition of certain assets and the complete set of intellectual property of Cakewalk Inc. from Gibson Brands on 2/23/18, BandLab Technologies announced the relaunch of SONAR as Cakewalk by BandLab - available free-to-download to all BandLab users worldwide. 

As of Feb 21st 2018, information elsewhere on this website may no longer be accurate. 

Close and browse the legacy Cakewalk website. 

Cakewalk is committed to protecting the privacy of all information provided by our users. Please read the privacy policy below.

Cakewalk collects information (such as mailing and email address) about users during their registration for certain sections of our website. Cakewalk will not disclose this information to third parties (unless we are required to do so by law) and will protect this information in accordance with our strict security and confidentiality standards. Cakewalk does not offer or allow the selling of any user provided information to third parties.

Users may opt in to receive information about products, services, clinics, presentations, and other news from us by email. Users that do not want to receive information from us by email may opt out at any time by visiting this web page <http://www.cakewalk.com/newsletter>

### Security of your Personal Information

Cakewalk is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. 

### Cookies, Beacons and Tagging

We and our vendors may use cookies and other technology such as web beacons or tagging to measure page visits to our site, most frequently viewed pages, the effectiveness of our ads, and to determine the display of content and advertising based on your interests all for the goal of improving your experience with us. These are anonymous and unidentifiable: They do not include any personal information including your name, address, phone number, email address, or anything that personally identifies you.

### Marketo

Lastly, we use Marketo cookies to help us create an appealing and engaging experience for you. If you submit information about yourself like your name, email, or company, Cakewalk may track your interactions with our newsletters and website, allowing us to optimize your experience and receive relevant information. You can read the [Marketo Privacy Policy here.](http://legal.marketo.com/privacy/)

### Cakewalk Analytics 

Products installed by Cakewalk may contain support for "Cakewalk Analytics." This data is used to develop the Software further, and to adapt it to user requirements, and to optimize it. Cakewalk Analytics data will not be shared with any other 3rd party companies outside of Cakewalk Inc. or the Gibson brands.

If the “Cakewalk Analytics“ function has been activated in the Software preferences, data about the use of the Software by the user are transferred to us in either anonymous form OR by connecting your Cakewalk account when there is an internet connection. Further information about Cakewalk Analytics can be found at [www.cakewalk.com/analytics](http://www.cakewalk.com/analytics). 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at one of the following addresses: 

http://www.cakewalk.com/About/contact.aspx 

or 

Cakewalk   
Attention: Internet Privacy Policy   
179 Lincoln Street   
Boston, MA 02111
